clmforex.com 2016-10-23

# 

Fh_lWYoFeb_Yo

1. Our Commitment                                              4. How We Collect Personal Information
Core Liquidity Markets Pty Ltd (“Core Liquidity Markets”,      Core Liquidity Markets collects personal information in a
“Core Liquidity”, “we”, or “us”) is committed to providing you number of ways, including:
with the highest levels of client service. We recognise that        directly from you, when you attend a face-to-face
your privacy is very important to you and we respect the            interview;
confidentiality of information and the privacy of individuals.      directly from you, when you provide information through
                                                                    a data collection form;
Your personal information will be treated strictly in
                                                                    directly from you, when you provide information via the
accordance with the “Australian Privacy Principles” in the
                                                                    telephone; and
Privacy Act 1988 (Cth.) and the “Private Sector Amendments”
                                                                    directly from you, via an e-mail or the Internet.
contained in the Privacy Amendment (Enhancing Privacy
Protection) Act 2012 (Cth.).
                                                               5. How We Use Your Personal Information
Further information on privacy in Australia may be obtained
by visiting the website or the Office of the Federal Privacy   Primarily, your personal information is used in order to:
Commissioner at www.oaic.gov.au                                     meet particular legislative and regulatory requirements;
                                                                    assist in providing services to you;
Core Liquidity Markets believes that this Privacy Policy            assist with any calls you make to us;
discloses how the personal information you provide to us and        communicate relevant information to you; and
our representatives, is collected, used, held, disclosed and        assist in product development, marketing, planning,
disseminated. We are committed to being open and                    administration and credit control procedures.
transparent about how we use your personal information.
                                                               Please keep in mind that, from time to time, we may provide
We encourage you to check our website regularly for any        you with direct marketing material. This will include e-mails,
updates to our Privacy Policy.                                 articles and newsletters that may be of interest to you.
                                                               If, at any time, you do not wish to receive this information any
2. Why We Collect Personal Information
                                                               further, you may contact us with this request. We will
Core Liquidity Markets is required to meet particular          endeavour to meet your request within 1 (one) week.
legislative and regulatory requirements which requires us to
                                                               We also maintain a “Register” for those individuals who do
collect certain personal information from you for the
                                                               not wish to receive direct marketing material.
purposes of:
    providing you with the relevant product or service;        For any marketing you receive as a result of our use of
    managing and administering the product or service; and     cookies, please see the section dealing with cookies below. In
    protecting against fraud.                                  particular, please note the information about how to manage
                                                               your preferences both personally and with any social media
3. Your Personal Information                                   websites.
Due to government regulations and the nature of the
                                                               6. When We Disclose Your Personal
products or services we provide, we are required to collect
personal information about you which can include, but is not   Information and Who We Disclose It to,
limited to, the below:                                         Including Cross Border Disclosures
    Name, Address and Telephone Number(s);                     In line with modern business practices common to many
    Date of Birth;                                             financial institutions and to meet your specific needs we may
    Email Address;                                             disclose your personal information to the organisations
    Occupation and Job Title;                                  described below.
    Transaction Details Associated with Your Trading through
    Us;                                                        The Corporations Act has provided the Australian Securities
    Additional Information Provided to Us and Recorded via     and Investments Commission ("ASIC") with the authority to
    Telephone;                                                 inspect certain personal information that is kept on our files
    Information You Provided to Us on Client Agreement         about you.
    Forms;                                                     We also collect information about you for the purpose of
    Nominated Bank Account Details;                            reporting to AUSTRAC under the Anti-Money Laundering and
    Statement of Assets and Liabilities;                       Counter-Terrorism Financing Act 2006.
    Information Regarding Guarantees of Company Accounts;
    Tax File Number;                                           For the purposes set out above, we may disclose your
    Employer Information; and                                  personal information to organisations outside Core Liquidity
    Voluntary Information                                      Markets.
Please note that you are not required by law to provide us     The organisations to which we disclose information may
with any of the personal information requested, however,       include:
without the information required, Core Liquidity Markets may        other product providers in order to manage or administer
not be able to provide you with any of the services or              your product or service;
assistance you have sought.                                         compliance consultants in order to ensure that our
                                                                    representatives are meeting our compliance standards;
                                                                                        1 | Privacy Policy | Core Liquidity Markets

    mailing houses;                                             7. Solicited Personal Information
    your professional advisers, including your solicitor or
    accountant as authorised by you;                            Without your consent we will not collect information about
    information technology service providers to maintain,       you that reveals your racial or ethnic origin, political opinions,
    review, and develop our business systems, procedures        religious or philosophical beliefs or affiliations, membership
    and infrastructure, including testing and/or upgrading our  of professional or trade association, membership of a trade
    computer systems;                                           union, details of health, disability, sexual orientation, or
    government and regulatory authorities and other             criminal record.
    organisations, as required or authorised by law, for        It is our policy that sensitive information will be used and
    example, to government or regulatory bodies for the         disclosed only for the purposes for which it was provided,
    purposes related to public health or safety, the            unless the customer agrees otherwise or the use or disclosure
    prevention or detection of unlawful activities or to        of this information is allowed by law, or when the information
    protect public revenue;                                     is necessary for the establishment, exercise or defence of a
    another authorised representative of Core Liquidity         legal claim.
    Markets if necessary;
    a potential purchaser/organisation involved in the          8. How We Store and Secure Your Personal
    proposed sale of our business for the purpose of due
    diligence, corporate re-organisation and transfer of all or
                                                                Information
    part of our business assets;                                Core Liquidity Markets keeps your personal information in
    where you have given your consent including your legal      your respective client file. These files are accessible to
    advisers; and                                               authorised personnel only and are appropriately secured out
    a new owner of our business that will require the transfer  of hours.
    of your personal information.
                                                                Your personal information may also be held on our computer
In addition, our employees and any outsourcing                  database.
companies/contractors are obliged to respect the
                                                                All computer-based information is protected through the use
confidentiality of any personal information held by Core
                                                                of access passwords. Data is backed up regularly and stored
Liquidity Markets.
                                                                securely off site. Some other measures taken are:
Core Liquidity Markets takes its obligations to protect your         Confidentiality requirements for our employees;
information seriously, this includes when we operate                 Security measures for system’s access; and
throughout Australia and overseas, as part of our operations.        Provision of a discreet environment for confidential
Some uses and disclosures of your information may occur              discussions.
outside your State or Territory and/or outside of Australia. In
                                                                Please note that personal information will be treated as
some circumstances we may need to obtain your consent
                                                                confidential information and sensitive information will be
before this occurs.
                                                                treated as highly confidential.
We may take reasonable steps to require organisations, both
                                                                It is a legislative requirement that we keep all personal
within and outside the Core Liquidity Markets’ group of
                                                                information and records for a period of 7 years. Should you
companies, who handle or obtain personal information as
                                                                cease to be a client of ours, we will maintain your personal
service providers to us, acknowledge the confidentiality of
                                                                information on or off site in a secure manner for 7 years. After
this information, undertake to respect any individual's right
                                                                this, the information will be destroyed.
to privacy and comply with either the Australian Privacy
Principles or their local privacy regime and this policy.
                                                                9. Ensure Your Personal Information is
Our ability to enforce the Australian Privacy Principles or any
                                                                Correct and Up-to-Date
other contractual privacy obligation against overseas
recipients and to take action in relation to any breach may be  Core Liquidity Markets takes all reasonable precautions to
very limited and/or far less effective than it would be if such ensure that the personal information we collect, use and
recipients were Australian based. As Australian Privacy         disclose is accurate, complete and up-to-date.
Principles may not be enforceable against or apply to
                                                                To ensure we can maintain this level of accuracy and
overseas regulation, we understand that you may choose not
                                                                completeness, we recommend that you:
to disclose your personal information to us. However, if you
                                                                     inform us of any errors in your personal information as
choose not to provide the information we need to fulfil your
                                                                     soon as possible; and
request for a specific product or service, we may not be able
                                                                     update us with any changes to your personal information
to provide you with the requested product or service.
                                                                     as soon as possible.
In the event of that we propose to sell the business, we may
                                                                We can generally update your customer information over the
disclose your personal information to potential purchasers for
                                                                telephone, by e-mail from your registered e-mail address.
the purpose of them conducting due diligence investigations.
                                                                Please note however that you may be asked to verify your
Disclosure will be made in confidence and it will be a
                                                                personal details for security purposes before an amendment
condition of that disclosure that no personal information will
                                                                can be made.
be used or disclosed by them.
                                                                                        2 | Privacy Policy | Core Liquidity Markets

If you provide inaccurate or incomplete information, we may      13. Our Complaint Resolutions
not be able to provide you with the products or services you
are seeking.                                                     Please contact our Privacy Officer if you wish to complain
                                                                 about any breach or potential breach of your privacy rights.
10. Access to Your Personal Information                          Generally, your complaint will be responded to within 7 days.
                                                                 If you are not satisfied with the outcome of your complaint,
You have a right to access your personal information, subject
                                                                 you are entitled to contact the Office of the Privacy
to certain exceptions allowed by law.
                                                                 Commissioner.
We ask that you provide your request for access in writing (for
                                                                 Please note that Core Liquidity Markets may record
security reasons) and we will provide you with access to that
                                                                 telephone conversations between you and any person
personal information.
                                                                 working for Core Liquidity Markets. Such recordings, or
Access to the requested personal information may include:        transcripts from such recordings, may be used for training
     providing you with copies;                                  purposes and to assist with the resolve of any dispute
     providing you with the opportunity for inspection; or       between you and Core Liquidity Markets.
     providing you with a summary.
If charges are applicable in providing access to you, we will    14. Our Website
disclose these charges to you prior to providing you with the    Please note that Core Liquidity Markets’ website provides
information.                                                     links to third party websites.
Some exceptions exist where we will not provide you with         The use of your information by these third party sites is not
access to your personal information, if:                         within the control of Core Liquidity Markets and we cannot
     providing access would pose a serious threat to the life or accept responsibility for the conduct of these organisations.
     health of a person;                                         Other websites are not subject to our privacy standards,
     providing access would have an unreasonable impact on       policies and procedures. You will need to contact or review
     the privacy of others;                                      those websites directly to ascertain their privacy stands,
     the request for access is frivolous or vexatious;           policies and procedures.
     the information is related to existing or anticipated legal
     proceedings between us and would not be discoverable        You may register with us to receive newsletters and other
     in those proceedings;                                       information. By doing so, your name and e-mail address will
     providing access would reveal our intentions in relation to be collected and stored on our database. We take care to
     negotiations with you in such a way as to prejudice those   ensure that the personal information you give us on our
     negotiations;                                               website is protected. For example, our website has electronic
     providing access would be unlawful;                         security systems in place, including the use of firewalls and
     denying access is required or authorised by or under law;   data encryption.
     and                                                         If you do not wish to receive any further information from us,
     providing access would be likely to prejudice certain       or if you wish to update your registration details, please e-
     operations by or on behalf of an enforcement body or an     mail your request through to us. We will endeavour to meet
     enforcement body requests that access not be provided       your request within 5 working days.
     on the grounds of national security.
                                                                 We may use cookie technology as part of our websites
Should we refuse you access to your personal information, we     statistical reporting. A “cookie” is a small piece of information
will provide you with a written explanation for that refusal.    sent by a website that is saved on your hard disk by your
                                                                 computer's browser. It holds information a site may need to
11. Using Government Identifiers                                 personalize your experience and to gather web site statistical
                                                                 data, such as which pages are visited, what is downloaded,
Although in certain circumstances we are required to collect
                                                                 the internet provider's domain name and country that our
government identifiers such as your tax file number,
                                                                 visitors come from and the addresses of sites visited
Medicare number or pension card number, we do not use or
                                                                 immediately before, and after, coming to our site. However,
disclose this information other than when required or
                                                                 none of this is associated with you as an individual. It is
authorised by law or unless you have voluntarily consented to
                                                                 measured only in aggregate. The information in the cookies
disclose this information to any third party.
                                                                 lets us trace your "click stream" activity (i.e., the paths taken
                                                                 by visitors to our site as they move from page to page). Please
12. Dealing with Us Anonymously                                  note that cookies do not capture your individual e-mail
You can deal with us anonymously where it is lawful and          address or any private information about you.
practicable to do so. For example, if you telephone requesting   If you wish to browse without cookies, you can configure your
our postal address.                                              browser to reject all cookies, or to notify you when a cookie
Please be advised however, due to the nature of the services     is set (note that each browser is different, so you will need to
and products we provide, and regulatory requirements             check the “help” menu of your browser to learn how to
associated, we cannot offer an option allowing you to            change your cookie preferences).
transact as client of ours on an anonymous basis.                Furthermore, we also use standard web server log files to
                                                                 help us count visitors and evaluate our site's technical
                                                                                          3 | Privacy Policy | Core Liquidity Markets

capacity. We use this information to find out how many          19. Comply with the Law Regarding Viral
people visit our site, help us arrange the pages in the most    Messages
user-friendly way, keep the site browser-friendly, and to
make our pages more useful to our visitors. We record           Core Liquidity Markets ensures that Commercial
information on site traffic but not information on individual   Communications that include a forwarding facility contain a
visitors to our site, so no information about you in particular clear recommendation that the Recipient should only forward
will be kept or used.                                           the Commercial Communication to persons with whom they
                                                                have a relationship, where that relationship means that
15. Spam Act                                                    person could be said to have consented to receiving
                                                                Commercial Communications.
“Spam” is a generic term used to describe electronic junk mail
or unwanted messages sent to a person’s e-mail account or       20. Contact Details
mobile phone.
                                                                Name:                          Core Liquidity Markets Pty Ltd
In Australia, spam is defined as ‘unsolicited commercial
electronic messages’.                                           Attention:                     Privacy Officer
‘Electronic messaging’ covers e-mails, instant messaging,       Address:                       Level 50
SMS and other mobile phone messaging, but do not cover                                         120 Collins Street
normal voice-to-voice communication by telephone.                                              Melbourne
                                                                                               VIC 3000
Core Liquidity Markets complies with the provisions of the                                     Australia
Spam Act when sending commercial electronic messages.
                                                                Phone (AUS):                   +61 2 8015 5431
Equally importantly, Core Liquidity Markets makes sure that
our practices are in accordance with the National Privacy       Phone (U.K.):                  +44 2 035 146 538
Principles in all activities where they deal with personal      E-mail:                        support@clmforex.com
information. Personal information includes our clients
contact details.                                                Website:                       www.clmforex.com
16. ‘Do not Call’ Register
Unless you ask us by calling +61 2 8015 5431, not to contact
you about our products or services and not to disclose your
information to others for that purpose, by accessing our
website, you consent to us to contact you via telephone while
you hold any product or receive any services from us
notwithstanding registration at any time of your telephone
number on the ‘do not call’ register.
17. Internal Procedure for Dealing with
Communications
The three key steps Core Liquidity Markets follows:
1. Consent – Only commercial electronic messages are sent
     with the addressee’s consent – either express or inferred
     consent.
2. Identify – Electronic messages will include clear and
     accurate information about the person and the company
     that is responsible for sending the commercial electronic
     message.
3. Unsubscribe – We ensure that a functional unsubscribe
     facility is included in all our commercial electronic
     messages and deal with unsubscribe requests promptly.
18. Consented to Such Communications
Commercial messages will only be sent to you when you have
given consent.
This may be express consent – a direct indication that it is
okay to send the message, or messages of that nature or
inferred consent based on our business or other relationship
with you and your conduct.
                                                                                     4 | Privacy Policy | Core Liquidity Markets
